const questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is the name of Phoebe's most famous song?",
      options: ["Smelly Cat", "Crazy Underwear", "Sticky Shoes", "Regina Phalange"],
      answer: "Smelly Cat"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "What does Joey never share?",
      options: ["Food", "His toothbrush", "His CDs", "His secrets"],
      answer: "His toothbrush"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "In which city did Friends take place?",
      options: ["New York", "Los Angeles", "Chicago", "Seattle"],
      answer: "New York"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "What is the name of Ross and Monica's dog when they were kids?",
      options: ["Max", "Rover", "Chi-Chi", "LaPooh"],
      answer: "Chi-Chi"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "What is the name of Joey's stuffed penguin?",
      options: ["Waddle", "Hugsy", "Flipper", "Mr. Ice"],
      answer: "Hugsy"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "What is the name of Ross's second wife?",
      options: ["Emily", "Carol", "Janice", "Rachel"],
      answer: "Emily"
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What is Chandler's middle name?",
      options: ["Michael", "Muriel", "Bing", "Francis"],
      answer: "Muriel"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Which character accidentally revealed Chandler and Monica's secret relationship?",
      options: ["Rachel", "Phoebe", "Joey", "Ross"],
      answer: "Rachel"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "What song makes Ross and Rachel's daughter, Emma, laugh for the first time?",
      options: ["Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star", "Baby Got Back", "I Will Always Love You", "The Lion Sleeps Tonight"],
      answer: "Baby Got Back"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "Who mistakenly threw a woman's wooden leg into a fire at Thanksgiving?",
      options: ["Joey", "Ross", "Monica", "Chandler"],
      answer: "Joey"
    },
  ];